marketersboard.com 2009-06-15

# Privacy And Disclosure Policies | The Success Doctor

At _SuccessDoctor.com_ , your privacy is assured. If you join the newsletter on this site, you will be kept posted on any developments that might benefit you. However, please note:

  * This site does not use "cookies" except for a single, nonidentifying one. It identifies you as a returning user but does not reveal any personal information about you. It's for the express purpose of limiting the number of times a pop-up appears, if any. This is done strictly for the convenience of users and not used for any other purpose. Any cookie or pop-up window blocking program will not interfere with the navigation or enjoyment of this site.  
 
  * This website does not gather personal information about you without your knowledge. Standard server log files are kept for the sole purpose of administering this site. They are not used for any other purpose. These files include user statistics, IP addresses (such as to identify geographic locations), user behavior (such as files requested), referrer URLs, time spent on each page, browsers, operating systems, and screen resolutions.  
 
  * Our mailing lists are and will remain completely confidential. They are not (and will never be) sold to, rented to or shared with anyone. Upon request, you will be promptly removed from the databases without any questions. (Please see below for easy removal instructions.) Although highly unlikely, a confirmation request will be emailed to you before any changes happen, if ever. **We respect your trust.**  
 
  * This site contains numerous links to other sites on the web. This site is not responsible for or has no control over the respective privacy practices of such sites. Please use discretion.

If you received unsolicited commercial information about this website or its offerings from an unknown third party (i.e., "spam"), please report the abuse to us immediately so that appropriate action can be taken, by using [this confidential form](http://www.successdoctor.com/contact/ "Contact The Success Doctor™").

Also, this site uses several third parties to handle certain business services. Great care was taken in their selection. But if you have received unsolicited email as a result of using these services, please do not hesitate to report it immediately as well. They will be discontinued immediately.

### To Opt-out or Modify

Users are provided with the opportunity to easily opt-out of receiving future communications from Michel Fortin, modify information they've provided, or remove them from Mike's databases. You may do so in the following ways:

  * **Online:** Directly by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.
  * **Email:** Contact tech support [on this page](http://www.successdoctor.com/contact/ "Contact The Success Doctor™") via email or online
  * **Mail:** 1707 Cara Crescent, Ottawa, Ontario K4A 1M4 (Canada)
  * **Telephone/Fax:** 613-482-4828

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn at any time that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems and databases.

_The Success Doctor_ encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer (you can also [check out the FTC's website](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm "FTC's guidelines on kids' only privacy") for more tips on protecting children's privacy online):

  * Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or adult guardian (includes name, address, phone, school, etc).
  * Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
  * Look for website privacy policies (and read them) of those visited by your child so you know how your child's information is treated.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy pledge or about the practices of this site, do not hesitate to [contact us](http://www.successdoctor.com/contact/ "Contact The Success Doctor™") at any time, in complete confidence, or call directly at (613) 482-4828. For more on privacy policies and guidelines, visit the [Online Privacy Alliance](http://www.privacyalliance.org/ "Online Privacy Alliance").

### Disclosure Policy

This policy is valid from 2nd of November, 2006. This site, and sites owned by and referenced from this site, are written and edited by Michel Fortin. For questions about this site, [please contact us](http://www.successdoctor.com/contact/ "Contact The Success Doctor™"). This website accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content. The owner(s) of this site is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics.

The views and opinions expressed on this site are purely this website’s owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement.

Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider. This site does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest. For more, or to get your own policy, go to [DisclosurePolicy.org](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/ "DisclosurePolicy.org").
